Guide to the Whitman College Communications Office Records 1895-2010
Whitman College and Northwest Archives
- Communications Office Records, 1958-2002; Series 3; 6 boxes
  - Harper Joy Theatre and “Black Comedy”, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 13/33)
  - Harper Joy Theatre and “Iolanthe”, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 13/34)
  - Harper Joy Theatre, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 13/35)
  - Harper Joy Theatre and music building renovations, 1983-1996 (Box-folder 13/36)
  - Harper Joy Theatre, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 13/37)
  - Homecoming, 1965-1976 (Box-folder 14/1)
  - Homecoming, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 14/2)
  - Horizon Air magazine, 1995 (Box-folder 14/3)
  - Whitman housing, security, and food service, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 14/4)
  - Human Development Center and Women’s Center, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 14/5)
  - “I Have a Dream” summer program, 1995 (Box-folder 14/6)
  - Incoming Whitman students, 1981-1989 (Box-folder 14/7)
  - Inner tube incident, 1997 (Box-folder 14/8)
  - Interim, 1970-1979 (Box-folder 14/9)
  - Interim, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 14/10)
  - Interim, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 14/11)
  - Interim, 1982 (Box-folder 14/12)
  - Interim, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 14/13)
  - Interim, 1984 (Box-folder 14/14)
  - Jackson, Paul memorial speech, 1976 (Box-folder 14/15)
  - Leary/Farris moral debate, 1981 (Box-folder 14/16)
  - Tristram Lundquist shooting, 1987 (Box-folder 14/17)
  - Marcus Whitman hotel, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 14/18)
  - Music: Whitman College Trio, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 14/19)
  - Guest musicians at Whitman College, 1968-1984 (Box-folder 14/20)
  - Penitentiary Social Therapy Program, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 14/21)
  - Salishan Conference, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 14/22)
  - Sheehan and Olin Galleries, 1976-1983 (Box-folder 14/23)
  - Sherwood Center dedication, 1969 (Box-folder 14/24)
  - Special events, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 14/25)
  - Stadium Controversy: Borleske Athletic Complex, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 14/26)
  - Summer Dance Lab, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 14/27)
  - Summer Dance Lab, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 14/28)
  - Summer Dance Lab, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 14/29)
  - Summer Dance Lab, 1983 (Box-folder 14/30)
  - Summer Dance Lab, 1984 (Box-folder 14/31)
  - Summer Dance Lab, 1985 (Box-folder 14/32)
  - “Trails West” amphitheatre production, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 14/33)
  - Young Republicans, 1976 (Box-folder 14/34)
  - Press releases, 1981-1983 (Box 15)
  - Press releases, 1983-1987 (Box 16)
- Newspaper clippings, 1895-2010; Series 4; 14 boxes
  - Newspaper engraving blocks, Undated (Box 17)
  - Clippings, “The Advance” magazine, “The Romance of a College” brochures, and Walter Bratton honorary booklet, 1895-1980 (Box-folder 18/1)
  - College Opinions, Economic Survey of Whitman College, Student Survey, newspaper and magazine clippings, news releases, and correspondence relating to Whitman College history, 1902-1989 (Box-folder 18/2)
  - Clippings relating to Greater Whitman, 1908 (Box-folder 18/3)
  - Clippings relating to Whitman College, 1908-1994 (Box-folder 18/4)
  - Clippings, notes, and “Reports of the Greater Whitman Campaign Fund”, 1909-1920 (Box-folder 18/5)
  - War department correspondence, newspaper clippings, list of graduates in service, programs, and sketches relating to college history, 1914-1981 (Box-folder 18/6)
  - Clippings relating to Whitman College, 1935-1943 (Box-folder 18/7)
  - Clippings relating to Whitman College, 1972 (Box-folder 18/8)
  - Clippings relating to Whitman College, 1973 (Box-folder 18/9)
  - Clippings relating to Whitman College, 1975 (Box-folder 18/10)
  - Clippings relating to Whitman College, 1976 (Box-folder 18/11)
  - Clippings relating to Whitman College, 1977 (Box-folder 18/12)
  - Clippings relating to Whitman College, 1978 (Box-folder 18/13)
  - Clippings relating to Whitman College, 1979 (Box-folder 18/14)
  - Clippings relating to Whitman College, 1981 (Box-folder 18/15)
  - Scrapbook, 1924 (Box 19)
  - Scrapbook, 1924-1925 (Box 20)
  - Scrapbook, 1934-1935 (Box 21)
  - Scrapbook, 1935-1936, 1939 (Box 22)
  - Clippings relating to Whitman College, 1979-1981 (Box 23)
  - Clippings relating to Whitman College, 1981-1983 (Box 24)
  - Clippings relating to Whitman College, 1983-1984 (Box 25)
  - Clippings relating to Whitman College, 1984-1986 (Box 26)
  - Clippings relating to Whitman College, 1986-1987 (Box 27)
  - Clippings, 1988-1990 (Box 28)
  - Clippings, 1991-1992 (Box 29)
  - Ethnic events, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 30/1)
  - Sports events, 1994 (Box-folder 30/2)
  - Hometown students, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 30/3)
  - Hometown students, 1997 (Box-folder 30/4)
  - “Whitman in the News”: books of newspaper articles about Whitman College, 2007-2010 (Box 31)
- Photographic material, 1915-2009; Series 5; 10 boxes
  - Photographs and negatives relating to the Whitman Conservatory of Music, social events, the Symphony Ball, and Whitman College buildings, circa 1915-1969 (Box 32)
  - Photograph negatives, including administrative officers and trustees, 1971-1975, 1980 (Box 33)
  - Photographic negatives, 1972-1979 (Box 34)
  - Photograph negatives, 1976-1978 (Box 35)
  - Photograph negatives, 1977-1989 (Box 36)
  - Photograph negatives, 1989-1992 (Box 37)
  - Photograph negatives, 1992-1995 (Box 38)
  - Slides and transparencies, circa 1976-1995 (Box 39)
  - Whitman faculty and staff, Scrambles outdoor program, and other miscellaneous, 1990-1996 (Box 40)
  - DVDs of college activity photographs, 1997-2009 (Box 41)